

Banjarmasin, South Kalimantan, Indonesia, 70248

+62 812 8440 3610

erwinmapaliey@gmail.com

in www.linkedin.com/in/erwinmapaliey/

erwmdevlab.com

github.com/erwinmapaliey

#### **PERSONAL DETAIL**

Date of Birth December 20th, 1994

#### **EDUCATION**

## Tenth Nopember Institute of Technology

Sarjana Komputer (S.Kom) - 2017 Major in Information System GPA 3.01 out of 4.00

#### **SKILLS**

### **Programming Languages**

PHP, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, SQL, Dart

#### Libraries & Frameworks

Laravel, Filament, Codeigniter, Inertia.js, Vue.js, Nuxt, React, Next.js, Tailwind CSS, Bootstrap CSS, Flutter

#### Tools & Platform

MySQL, PostgreSQL, Firebase, Git, GitHub, Gitlab, Vercel, Docker, Figma, Cloud Server

# **ERWIN WILBERT MAPALIEY**

#### SOFTWARE ENGINEER

#### **ABOUT ME**

I'm a software engineer since 2017 focusing on web development and just learning about mobile development. I have experience in developing web-based analytical dashboard & web apps using Laravel. Mostly work as backend developer but sometimes work as fullstack developer depends on team & project requirement.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### Senior Software Engineer - PT Suitmedia Kreasi Indonesia Oct 2022 - Present

- Develop and maintain web-based monolith application developed using Laravel, implement frontend side using Vue, develop CMS, database design, setup project on staging & production server, and also create technical documentation.
- Work with junior developer, review code & merge on GitLab.
- Mentoring intern developer on project team.

#### Notable Project:

- Adhi Karya e-SCM Enhancement (2022 2024)
- MOST Forum Mandiri Sekuritas (2022)

# Fullstack Web Developer - PT Hasnur Informasi Teknologi Jan 2018 - Jun 2022 SAP ABAP Developer Nov 2017 - Jan 2018

- Build and maintain web-based project to support other entity in company's group. Develop both frontend and backend system, mostly use PHP MVC Framework such as Codeigniter or Laravel with SAPRFC integration for main data source.
- Support SAP Functional Team as ABAP Developer, develop and enhance some SAP Modules based on request.
- Responsible in several web based project using SAPRFC.
- · Create Technical Documentation.

#### Notable Project:

- HG Mobile Attendance (2022)
- Employee Self Service (ESS) Web App Enhancement (2022)
- Vessel Tracker & Management Dashboard PT Hasnur Internasional Shipping (2021)
- MSU Dashboard (Tyre Module) PT Magma Sigma Utama (2020 2021)
- Agribusiness EIS (Executive Information System) PT Hasnur Citra Terpadu & PT Barito Putera Plantation (2018 - 2020)

#### **COURSE & CERTIFICATE**

- Git & GitHub The Practical Guide
  Udemy Online Course Jun 2022
- Flutter & Dart The Practical Guide
  Udemy Online Course Jun 2022
- Master Laravel, Vue 3, Inertia, Tailwind (VILT Stack)
   Udemy Online Course Oct 2024